0xBitcoin is the first fully decentralized ERC20 token
0xBitcoin เป็นโทเค็น ERC20 แรกที่ไร้ตัวกลางอย่างสมบูรณ์
and is the first purely mined token on Ethereum
และยังเป็นโทเค็นแรกที่ขุดจนหมดจดบนอีเธอเรียม
and it aims to be the primary medium of exchange
และมีเป้าหมายเพื่อเป็นวิธีหลักในการแลกเปลี่ยน
and store of value on the Ethereum network.
และเก็บค่าไว้ในเครือข่ายอีเธอเรียม
The 0xBitcoin token was deployed to the Ethereum blockchain in
ปรับใช้โทเค็น 0xBitcoin กับบล็อกเชนอีเธอเรียมใน
February 2018 with the following attributes:
เดือนกุมภาพันธ์ 2018 ด้วยคุณสมบัติดังต่อไปนี้:
first mineable token,
โทเค็นแรกที่ขุดได้
ERC20 compatible,
ใช้ร่วมกับ ERC20 ได้
no pre-mine or instamine,
ไม่มีการ pre-mine หรือ instamine
and no ICO.
และไม่มี ICO
Ether was never intended to act as a currency, and
อีเธอร์จะไม่เป็นสกุลเงินและ
0xBitcoin will allow Ether to fulfill its sole intended purpose
0xBitcoin จะช่วยให้อีเธอร์บรรลุวัตถุประสงค์ที่ตั้งไว้เพียงอย่างเดียว
of securing the Ethereum network.
ของการรักษาความปลอดภัยเครือข่ายอีเธอเรียม
0xBitcoin takes the best properties of Bitcoin and Ethereum
0xBitcoin ใช้คุณสมบัติที่ดีที่สุดของบิทคอยน์และอีเธอเรียม
and combines them into one token.
และรวมเป็นโทเค็นเดียว
It can be mined exactly like Bitcoin
ขุดได้เหมือนบิทคอยน์
but transferred 10 times faster and 100 times cheaper.
แต่โอนได้เร็วกว่า 10 เท่าและถูกกว่า 100 เท่า
0xBitcoin combines the Bitcoin properties of
0xBitcoin รวมคุณสมบัติของบิทคอยน์ในเรื่อง
block rewards, proof-of-work issuance,
ผลตอบแทน การออก proof-of-work
and a 21 million coin cap
และมูลค่าเหรียญ 21 ล้าน
with the Ethereum properties of
กับคุณสมบัติอีเธอเรียมของ
speed, DApps, and DEX trading.
ความเร็ว, DApps และการซื้อขาย DEX
And unlike Ether, it interfaces with smart contracts
และไม่เหมือนอีเธอร์ตรงที่ทำงานร่วมกับสัญญาอัจฉริยะ
for storing and transferring value.
ในการจัดเก็บและถ่ายโอนค่า
While Bitcoin can only be traded using centralized means,
แต่บิทคอยน์ซื้อขายได้โดยใช้วิธีที่มีตัวกลางเท่านั้น
0xBitcoin can be traded permissionlessly via
ซื้อขาย 0xBitcoin ได้โดยไม่ต้องได้รับอนุญาตผ่านทาง
smart contracts which cannot be affected or controlled
สัญญาอัจฉริยะที่จะไม่มีผลกระทบหรือควบคุมได้
by central entities.
โดยหน่วยงานกลาง
It is also immune to 51% attacks.
นอกจากนี้ ยังมีภูมิคุ้มกันต่อการโจมตีถึง 51%
Add all this to the proven market demand for a
เพิ่มทั้งหมดนี้ไปยังความต้องการของตลาดที่พิสูจน์แล้วสำหรับ
faster version of Bitcoin, as we've seen in
บิทคอยน์รุ่นที่เร็วกว่า ตามที่เราเห็น
Litecoin's success, and it is plain that
ความสำเร็จของไลท์คอยน์ และก็ชัดเจนว่า
0xBitcoin fills a hole in the crypto market space.
0xBitcoin เติมเต็มในพื้นที่ตลาด crypto
People are excited about the project in no small part due to
ผู้คนตื่นเต้นกับโครงการนี้มากเนื่องจาก
the decentralization of the token
การกระจายศูนย์กลางของโทเค็น
and the active and engaged community
และมีชุมชนใช้งานและมีส่วนร่วมอยู่
which has sprung up around the token.
ซึ่งเกิดขึ้นรอบๆ โทเค็น
The community has achieved several key milestones
ชุมชนได้บรรลุเป้าหมายสำคัญหลายประการ
since the project's launch, including
ตั้งแต่เปิดตัวโครงการ รวมถึง
creating an EIP specifically for mineable tokens,
การสร้าง EIP สำหรับโทเค็นที่ขุดได้โดยเฉพาะ
creation of mining pools with multiple new mining clients,
สร้างแหล่งขุดกับลูกค้าใหม่หลายราย
as well as ongoing development of Lava Wallet,
รวมถึงการพัฒนา Lava Wallet
Quarry, and off-chain transactions.
แอป Quarry และธุรกรรมนอกบล็อกเชนอย่างต่อเนื่อง
0xBitcoin is a unique project, backed by a passionate community
0xBitcoin เป็นโครงการที่ไม่เหมือนใครซึ่งได้รับการสนับสนุนโดยชุมชนผู้หลงใหล
dedicated to making it the primary transfer of value
ที่ทุ่มเทที่จะทำให้โครงการนี้เป็นการถ่ายโอนค่าหลัก
for the Ethereum network.
ของเครือข่ายอีเธอเรียม